

Inês Hermínio





As a Full Stack Web Developer, I have a wealth of experience in building and maintaining web applications. I am an analytical and creative individual who is constantly motivated to learn and grow. My previous career, as Marketing and Strategic Manager, has provided valuable skills and experience that continue to enhance my abilities as a web developer. I am excited to continue this chapter of my professional journey and look forward to the challenges and rewards that come with being a web developer.

Full Stack · Web Dev · Web2 · Web3 · New Challenges

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Momentum One

Full Stack Web Developer since mar 2022

 Lead developer, both Frontend and BackendResponsible for the Backend implementation of Hermes Protocol - the first notification & communication platform for any on-chain (web3) alerts delivered on social media

RELEVANT PORTFOLIO

Hermes Protocol

React, Node.js, FaunaDB, Cloudflare

Notifications-as-a-Service that bridges Web2 and Web3

Pet Log

MERN Stack, Leaflet

A mobile-first app, created to help pet owners manage their pets' life

EDUCATION

Ironhack

Full Stack Web Development • Bootcamp jun 2021 to dec

- · Responsive design with HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- · Back-end: Server-side and data modeling complexity
- · Single-page applications using React.js and the MERN stack

SheCodes Academy

Introduction to Coding may 2021

NOVA School of Business and Economics

Management, Major in Marketing • Masters sep 2012 to ian 2014

Management • Undergraduate sep 2009 to jul 2012

SKILLS

Hard Skills

HTML5 MongoDB Express
CSS3 FaunaDB Cloudflare
JavaScript(ES6) REST APIs React
TypeScript GraphQL Vue
SQL Node.js Next.js

Soft Skills

- · Completing tasks and attaining goals
- · Meeting deadlines and time management
- Flexibility and adapting

Linguistic Skills









Native

Full Professional Proficiency

Elementary Proficiency

Elementary Proficiency

PREVIOUS CAREER

novobanco

Marketing & Strategic Manager jul 2019 to dec 2021

· Boost initiatives for business development, report and control

Tranquilidade

Marketing Manager sep 2017 to jul 2019

Distribution channel's development, initiatives, report and control

Galp Energia

Continuous Improvement Analyst nov 2016 to sep 2017

· New CRM Gas&Power project release

Allianz Portugal

Strategic Analyst feb 2014 to nov 2016

 Company's performance analysis and control, internal and Group reporting, processes' improvement and automation